hey everyone caffeine man here and today
we're adding another healthier energy
drink to the series for today's
healthier energy drink it's not your
typical energy drink it's called
Sparkling Ice plus caffeine it's from
the makers of Sparkling Ice if you
couldn't guess and they decided they're
going to be jumping into the caffeinated
beverage Market with this beverage and
I'm excited to try it out with you guys
today coming right
[Music]
up hey again everybody thanks for
joining me today if it's your first time
here feel free to hit the subscribe
subribe button I post new videos every
Tuesday night and for those of you who
have been here before you may not have
noticed but I started to add to the
description box some time stamps for you
guys with 12 to 15 minute long videos
not everyone wants to hear me blab on
and on on about the company they just
want to get right to the taste test and
then there are those of you that care
about the extra information such as the
nutritional facts as well as the taste
test so for those of you who are too
lazy to watch the whole video feel free
to check out my description box and go
wherever you want to go I won't be
offended that's why I put them there for
you guys so in today's video I'm going
to talk a little bit about the company
then I'll go over the ingredients that
make this drink a healthier energy drink
and then in closing I'll taste test all
five flavors that they have the five
flavors are blue raspberry black
raspberry triple citrus strawberry
Citrus and Orange passion fruit
Sparkling Ice is owned by a company
called talking rain Beverage Company
talking rain began in 1987 with two
Sparkling Waters in 1992 the company
began production of sparkling ICE
Sparkling Ice was basically just flavor
sparkling water then in 1997 the company
decided to change over at sweetener to
sucos becoming the first US Beverage
Company to do so then in 2014 Kevin
Durant a famous basketball player signed
an endorsement deal with sparkling ice
and then things really began to take off
for the company and they were recognized
in Inc 5000 additionally at that time
with the rise of healthier drinks being
on the market this flavored sparkling
water was now being compared as a
healthy alternative to drinking soda and
in October of 2018 not too long ago they
released their Sparkling Ice plus
caffeine flavor line the original
Sparkling Ice beverage line are made
with zero sugar combined with sparkling
water real fruit flavor vitamins and
antioxidants to offer a lightly
carinated beverage they have over 17
different flavors in their regular line
and now they just added five slightly
different flavors to their line with the
caffeine now some of you might be saying
hey you mentioned real fruit if there's
real fruit flavor in there isn't there
some sugar but Sparkling Ice only has 1%
juice in their beverages therefore it
only contains Trace Amounts of sugar
which by FDA standards is significant
luckily for all of you guys you don't
need to worry about it because the
Sparkling Ice plus caffeine doesn't have
any fruit juices therefore no sugar they
use sucos instead these drinks are also
kosher and gluten-free but they're not
vegan the reason being there's a small
amount of lanolin in the vitamin blend
and lanoline is a byproduct of Shar wool
so are these actually energy drinks well
the definition of energy can be quite
complex and I'm no scientist but there
are those that say caffeine gives you
energy there therefore any kind of
beverage with caffeine in it is an
energy drink but there are also those
that argue caffeine doesn't give you
energy caffeine helps produce energy
which is a very fine line really
therefore they say that if energy drinks
don't have all the other ingredients to
help boost your energy if it just has
caffeine it's not an energy drink but
you know what I say to that I say what's
my name is my name Energy Drink Man no
it's caffeine man these drinks have
caffeine so I'm going over them all the
rest you can take your energy drink to
bait someplace else so what's the new
nutrition facts panel have to say about
this let's take a look zero calories
zero fat zero sodium zero carbs zero
sugar zero protein so far so good on to
the vitamins this has 10% of your daily
value of vitamin A it also has 10% of
Vitamin D it also has 10% of niin then
when you take a look at the B6 it also
has 10% B6 but when you look at the B12
it also has 10% of vitamin B12 and in
keeping in line with all their other
numbers the itin and panthic acid also
have 10% each so yes this is an energy
drink because it has all those other
energy drink properties in it but if you
know anything about energy drinks you'll
know that all those numbers are fairly
low but at least it'll shut up all those
energy drink arguments oh it's sparkling
water with caffeine no no no it's got
all that other stuff in it therefore
it's an energy drink might just be a
little bit of the stuff but it's still
an energy drink as for the caffeine
let's get right into it this 16 oz can
has 70 Mig of caffeine 70 yeah only 70
now for those caffeine lovers like me
you might be a little saddened by that
but you got to take in consideration
that there are a lot of people out there
that can't handle their caffeine like us
I mean there's a lot of people out there
that are looking for healthier energy
drinks but they don't want to go too
crazy like some companies
do with 300 migs of caffeine that's a
lot BCAAs CQ10 do they really need that
if they're not going to be working out
or even if they're just going to be
doing a late workout a lot of people
don't need all the extra stuff that's in
here there are other energy drinks out
there that have just a little bit of
what you need and sometimes more isn't
better so if you look at something
that's lightly caffeinated and has
vitamins in it Sparkling Ice plus
caffeine might be for you because there
are definitely people some people that
are sensitive to caffeine some of us can
take 300 Mig of caffeine and function
fine with it most people take 300 Mig of
caffeine and they get a good Boost from
it and there are also some people that
if they had 300 Mig of caffeine at noon
they still wouldn't be able to sleep at
night therefore people that are
sensitive to caffeine but still like to
have a little bit of caffeine to keep
them going can have this beverage this
beverage comes in at just slightly 4
migr per ounce making it the lowest
amount of caffeine out of all the energy
drinks for those of you who consider it
an energy drink and with those numbers
it actually fits in much closer to where
soda averages for caffeine content so
let's jump right into this taste test
first let's start off with the black
raspberry
wow that's actually pretty good as many
of you may know if you watch my previous
videos I'm not a fan of sparkling water
and I'm not really a fan of sparkling
beverages but there have been several
that have surprised me this one is one
of the ones that's surprising me I can't
taste any sparkling water flavor but I
can definitely taste the black raspberry
now it's not an overly powerful black
raspberry flavor but it's got a decent
amount of black raspberry flavor and the
sweetness is just enough with the sucos
if I didn't know that this was sparkling
water I probably wouldn't guess that it
was sparkling water I would think it's
more like a diet soda so great job
competing with the sodas for diet soda
this is a great healthy energy drink
that doesn't taste healthy I like things
that are healthy that don't taste
healthy if that makes sense you guys
know what I mean by healthy taste right
all right next up we got the blue
raspberry
oh wow that one's actually pretty good
too it's definitely different than the
black raspberry it's a bit sweeter than
the black raspberry and it's got a taste
of blueberry to it too which I'm
guessing is why they call it blue
raspberry I wasn't expecting the
blueberry and I like blueberry so that's
a bonus for me like I said it's a little
bit sweeter than the black raspberry but
it's not overly sweet it's definitely
not like bang or rain for the sweetness
but it's got a good sweetness to it and
it definitely tastes like a blue
raspberry I'm so glad I decided to do
this review I randomly saw him at the
store and said oh Sparkling Ice my wife
likes those drinks I had tried them once
and thought they were pretty good I
actually thought it was diet soda and
she said no it's flavored sparkling
water so I was at the convenience store
they said oh look caffeinated Sparkling
Ice let me try it and pick it up I'm
glad I did these are good next on to the
strawberry
Citrus I like strawberry not a huge fan
of citrus so let's see how it goes
H it's interesting it's not bad it's
pretty good I was expecting to be hit
with a strong sweet strawberry flavor
based on the blue raspberry but it's not
too sweet and the strawberry is kind of
light as for the Citrus flavor it's got
a hint of orange in there it's also got
a hint of lime in there and I think the
strawberry the orange and the lime are
all around the same amount so one's not
overpowering the other which is really
interesting cuz you get a hint of
strawberry a hint of orange a hint of
lime and nothing's really overpowering
the other and when you don't have
anything overpowering the other you
don't end up having an aftertaste of any
one of those flavors they all blend
together really well it's still not my
Top Choice I'm going with blue raspberry
first and then this one probably ties
for second with black raspberry but
still got two more to go so let's try
those out next up let's try the triple
citrus so how's the triple citrus
different than the strawberry Citrus if
you look at the pictures on the can the
strawberry Citrus has a picture of
strawberry orange and lime the triple
citrus has a picture of an orange Al
lime and I think maybe a lemon the color
is very close to the orange though but
I'm guessing it's a lemon but let's stop
guessing and try it
out oh yeah that's definitely lemon this
is your classic lemon lime soda with a
hint of orange to it I would say it's
similar to like a Diet Sprite but as we
all know Soda is bad for you so it's not
but the FL is similar to a Diet Sprite
and this is super healthy so pick this
up over Sprite any day these are really
good caffeine Man's having a happy day
or it could be because I'm drinking five
energy drinks last on the list Orange
passion fruit do I talk faster at the
end of my videos I feel like by the time
I get to the last two they go pretty
fast try and slow it down a little bit
but I don't want the videos to be too
long so let's keep going
all right Orange passion fruit the
Orange is the strongest out of all the
Citrus ones that I've had and the
passion fruit is a bit light but it's
still there personally I'd like it to be
just a touch sweeter but that's just my
preference it's still lightly sweetened
and the strong orange flavor is a little
bit too acidic for me which is why I
usually like the sweetness cut into that
bite a little bit as for passion fruit
I'm not a huge fan of passion fruit but
it's still light so it's not bad I
definitely say try it for your for
yourself if you like Orange passion
fruit because from the other four this
tastes like it's pretty good even though
I personally don't like passion fruit
that much it's still a good flavor and
based on the other four flavors this is
probably a really good Orange passion
fruit so overall I'm impressed with all
five of those these have the perfect
amount of Sweetness in it and if you're
looking for something that's similar to
a soda beverage but diet without all the
negativity of soda you can try these out
they're really good you can kind of tell
their diet because it's a sparkling
beverage with sucos but out of the
healthy energy drinks that I've reviewed
so far between a spire Celsius your
bmate and now Sparkling Ice I'm a fan of
the Sparkling Ice flavor the most I'm
not a fan of the lack of caffeine but I
like the flavors and sometimes I freely
admit this I don't want to have a 300 mg
beverage sometimes in the morning while
I'm driving to work I need that little
bit to pick me up to get me to work so
why not have a 70 migr caffeine drink to
start your morning it's almost the same
amount as a cup of coffee and there you
have it another healthy energy drink in
the books feel free to leave me a
comment down below I love comments by
most of you summer you you know who you
are and feel free to subscribe if you
haven't I post new videos every Tuesday
night and hope to see you there until
next time have a great
day or night